pay4tweet.com 2010-01-19

# Online

Online Privacy Statement
Effective December 15, 2009
Thank you for visiting PAY4TWEET.com. Our Online Privacy Statement is designed to inform you about
our collection and use of personal information on this web site. From time to time, may modify this
Online Privacy Statement.
The Online Privacy Statement is available on the home page of this web site as well as at every point on
the web site where you provide us with personal information. From time to time, you may click to other
PAY4TWEET web sites that have different privacy policies. See "PAY4TWEET's Web Site May Be Linked to
Other Web Sites" below.
This privacy policy only applies to the information we collect on the PAY4TWEET.com website. This
privacy policy does not apply to information we collect through other methods or sources, including
sites owned or operated by our affiliates, vendors or partners.
The Only Personal Information We Collect Online is Information You Voluntarily Provide to Us.
The only information we collect about you on this web site is information that you voluntarily provide to
us. This information may include, for example, name, mailing address, email address, phone number and
similar information. If you supply us with personal information on this web site, we will use that
information only to contact you so that we can:
  1. provide you with the information you have requested (press releases, investor information),
  2. follow up on job opportunities that you have inquired about, or
  3. occasionally send you other information about PAY4TWEET and its services that we believe you
would find interesting.
This information will not be sent to you via email unless you ask us to do so.
When You Browse the PAY4TWEET Web Site, You Do So Without Revealing Your Identity.
This PAY4TWEET web site may use cookies to aggregate information about the pages that users visit so
that we can update and redesign, as necessary, our web site in order to provide you with the most
useful information. Personal information, such as your email address, is not collected, unless you
provide it to us. PAY4TWEET does not disclose domain name or aggregate information to third parties
other than vendors who assist us with our web site and who are under strict confidentiality
requirements. From time to time, however, we may disclose this information to fulfill legal or regulatory
obligations or if we determine such disclosure is legally advisable or necessary to protect our rights, the
rights of others, or to prevent harm. In addition, we may aggregate data about users of our site and use

it for statistical purposes. This information helps us to better understand our site’s users and how to
improve our site and our offerings.
We Are Committed to Protecting the Confidentiality of User Information.
PAY4TWEET's policies limit access to personal user information that is collected from this web site to
those employees of PAY4TWEET and its affiliates and business partners who need the information to
fulfill their business responsibilities. PAY4TWEET may disclose personal information collected online to
companies affiliated with PAY4TWEET in connection with employment opportunities in those
companies, to our vendors who assist us with the web site, or to outside recruiters in connection with
employment offers. In some cases, this may require your information to be sent to other countries. By
supplying your information on this web site, you consent to your information being transferred across
national borders to PAY4TWEET, its affiliates, vendors or agents. Vendors and other outside contractors
we engage are subject to our contractual requirements to ensure that personal information is
safeguarded. Employees and others with duties related to this web site must adhere to this Online
Privacy Statement. Any employee violating this Online Privacy Statement may be subject to disciplinary
action, up to and including dismissal.
As noted above, from time to time, however, we may disclose this information to fulfill legal or
regulatory obligations or if we determine such disclosure is legally advisable or necessary to protect our
rights, the rights of others, or to prevent harm. In addition, we may aggregate data about users of our
site and use it for statistical purposes. This information helps us to better understand our site’s users
and how to improve our site and our offerings.
 We Give Web Site Users a Choice about How Their Information Will be Used.
In some instances, if we collect information online, we will inform users at that point about how to
remove their names from our lists.
We Use Appropriate Security Safeguards.
At PAY4TWEET, security is a priority. PAY4TWEET employs appropriate measures, including advanced
technology, to protect personal information collected online against unauthorized access, disclosure,
alteration or destruction. These measures may include, among others, encryption, physical access
security, and other appropriate technologies. PAY4TWEET continually reviews and enhances its security
systems, as necessary.

PAY4TWEET's Web Site May Be Linked to Other Web Sites.
As you navigate our site, you may click to web sites of our different subsidiaries and divisions. Those
web sites may have their own online privacy statements or policies. This Online Privacy Statement will
not apply when you move to one of these other sites because business unit privacy practices and
policies are tailored to the products and services offered by the individual PAY4TWEET business units. As
you visit the pages and sites of our different business units please be sure to review the privacy policies
applicable to those sites.
PAY4TWEET may create links to third‐party web sites. PAY4TWEET is not responsible for the content or
privacy practices employed by web sites that are linked to our web site.
